dobovo.com 2013-12-05

# Privacy Policy

### Recently Ordered

[](http://www.dobovo.com/simferopol-apartments/railway-station-SF1458.html) |  Studio  
Railway Station  
16 hours ago

UAH 253.00  
  
---|---  
[](http://www.dobovo.com/simferopol-apartments/in-the-city-center-with-internet-SF1942.html) |  Studio  
In the city center with Internet  
yesterday

UAH 287.50  
  
[](http://www.dobovo.com/) |  Studio  
Apartment in the city center  
yesterday

UAH 287.50  
  
### Customer Reviews

“ City is very beautiful. Apartment was excellent. We liked everything.”

**Анна** , (Ukraine)  
_27 December, 2011_

### FAQ

Last Updated: June 23, 2013

**Dobovo.com and International Booking Center LLC**. (“Dobovo”, “we” or “us”) informs users of our polices and procedures through this Privacy Policy. How we collect, use and disclose personal information we receive from users of: [www.dobovo.com](http://www.dobovo.com/) (the “Site”) is detailed herein.

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time and applies only to information that you provide to us through the the Site. Changes in our information practices may be updated in this Privacy Policy. If we make any major changes we will notify you by putting a notice on the Site prior to the change becoming effective. We ask you to review this page from time to time for the latest information. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used on this page mean the same as in our Terms of Service (<http://www.dobovo.com/terms-and-conditions.html>). The terms “processing” and “using” information include setting/getting cookies information, subjecting the information to analyze statistics and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to storing, evaluating, deleting, modifying, collecting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within Ukraine or internationally.

**Gathering and Storing of Personally-Identifying Information**

Our main goals in gathering information are to improve our Site and to administer your use of the Site and to enable all users to easily navigate and enjoy it. Please note, that information we collect may be transfered to and stored on servers where privacy laws might not be as protective as those where you located. If you are located outside of Ukraine and decide to use the Site, your personal information will be transfered to Ukraine and processed here. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by submission of such information means your agreement to that transfer.

When you register as an owner, add accommodation, make a booking or contact accommodation owner we will ask you for personally identifiable information which include information about yourself that can be used to contact or identify you (“Identity Information”). Identity Information includes, but is not limited to, your name, email address, phone number, postal address, but does not include your credit card number or any other billing information. We also collect the other information that you provide as part of registration and the administration and personalization of your Dobovo Account profile (e.g., without limitation, zip code (on its own) and individual preferences or demographic information) (“Non-Identifying Information”). We use your Personal Information (in some cases, in conjunction with your Non-Identifying Information) mainly to in Site functions, to complete your transactions, and administer your inquiries.

If you are an accommodation owner registered in our system, we also use your Personal Information to contact you with Dobovo newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please update your “Notifications” settings. (See “Changing or Deleting Information,” below.) Please note that we may also use your Personal Information to contact you with information related to your use of the Site; you may not opt out of these notifications.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small data file that a website stores on visitor's computer. We use cookies to help identify and track your visits of the Site, your usage of Site, and your Site access preferences. If you do not wish to have cookies placed on your computer, you can instruct your browser to refuse and disable cookies, with the drawback that certain features of Site may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information**

**Accommodations Listing**

If you add an accommodation listing, you agree to publicly publish that listing via the Site and enable third parties to publish your listing on their websites through the use of our partnership program. We also display your actual street address of the building - the geographical location of your listing in the form of a map so that potential Guests can see the area and neighborhood of your listing.

**Aggregated Statistics**

Our Site may contain single-pixel images which are commonly used along with cookies to collect aggregated statistics in order to analyze how our Site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This provides us with a possibility to gauge the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns and communications. We may share aggregated information that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and statistics data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information.

**Advertising Partners and Service Providers**

We may employ third party companies and individuals to perform maintenance services, database management, web analytics, fraud detection services relating to the activity of Dobovo Users and improvement of the Site features or to assist us in analyzing how our Site is used. These third parties may have access to your Personal Information; if they do, this access is only so that they may perform these tasks on our behalf and they are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose. We may also provide Personal Information to our business partners or other trusted entities for the purpose of providing you with information on goods or services we believe will be of interest to you. You can, at any time, opt out of receiving such communications. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on an Dobovo User’s prior visits to Dobovo. You can disable these specific cookies that track prior visits for the sake of follow-up advertising by opting out at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with the Site. The techniques our partners employ do not collect your Personal Information. You can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/ to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
